{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.5.5","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":855,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":13,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":true,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Button_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17767","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si17781","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide5444","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Button_7","si17767","si17781","Click_Box_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5444"}}},{"id":"si12318","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si12326","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12330","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12326_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The doctor\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12337","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12341","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12337_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The admitting nurse\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si15611","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15615","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15611_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A family member\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15626","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15630","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15626_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Theyâ€™re available at the front door\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12384","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si12434","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12274q0","for":"Slide12274q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12451","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12274q0","for":"Slide12274q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12464","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12274q0","for":"Slide12274q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12274q0","for":"Slide12274q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12409","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12274q0","for":"Slide12274q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12422","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12274q0","for":"Slide12274q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12388","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si12311","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12476","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12274q0","for":"Slide12274q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12493","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12274q0","for":"Slide12274q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12506","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12274q0","for":"Slide12274q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12274","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si12330","si12341","si15615","si15630","si12434","si12451","si12464","si12392","si12409","si12422","si12311","si12476","si12493","si12506"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12274"},"question":{"interactionId":"12291","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Who gives the patient theirDischarge Folder at Admission?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Slide17633","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17633"}}},{"id":"si15959","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"1","roles":{}},{"id":"si15915","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15919","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15915_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Throw it away\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15930","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15926_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Give it back to the nurse\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si15937","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15941","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15937_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Put important information in it\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si15948","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15952","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15948_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Nothing, leave it on the table\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16021","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16200q1","for":"Slide16200q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16033","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16200q1","for":"Slide16200q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16045","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16200q1","for":"Slide16200q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16200q1","for":"Slide16200q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16075","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16200q1","for":"Slide16200q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16200q1","for":"Slide16200q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_13","roles":{}},{"id":"si16162","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_3","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16200q1","for":"Slide16200q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16200q1","for":"Slide16200q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16186","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16200q1","for":"Slide16200q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15978","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","roles":{}},{"id":"si16138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_12","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16200","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si15919","si15930","si15941","si15952","si16021","si16033","si16045","si16063","si16075","si16087","si16162","si16174","si16186","si16138"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16200"},"question":{"interactionId":"15875","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What does a patient do with theirfolder during their hospital stay?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["3"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Slide17672","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17672"}}},{"id":"si16315","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"1_2","roles":{}},{"id":"si16271","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16275","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16271_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_9","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Take the folder home with them\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16282","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16286","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16282_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_10","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Nothing, leave it on the table\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16293","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16297","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16293_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_11","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Throw it away\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16304","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16308","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16304_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_12","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Give it back to the nurse\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16542","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","roles":{}},{"id":"si16371","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16556q2","for":"Slide16556q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16383","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16556q2","for":"Slide16556q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16395","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16556q2","for":"Slide16556q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16413","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16556q2","for":"Slide16556q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16425","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16556q2","for":"Slide16556q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16437","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16556q2","for":"Slide16556q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16494","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","roles":{}},{"id":"si16512","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16556q2","for":"Slide16556q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16524","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16556q2","for":"Slide16556q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16536","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16556q2","for":"Slide16556q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16488","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16556","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16275","si16286","si16297","si16308","si16371","si16383","si16395","si16413","si16425","si16437","si16512","si16524","si16536","si16488"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16556"},"question":{"interactionId":"16231","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What happens to the folder when a patient discharges from the hospital?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Slide17712","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17712"}}},{"id":"si17027","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"1_4","roles":{}},{"id":"si16983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16987","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16983_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_17","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cash\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16994","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16998","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16994_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_18","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All bills\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17005","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17009","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17005_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_19","roles":{"answer":{"title":"E.O.B.â€™s (Explanation of Benefits)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si17016","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17020","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17016_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_20","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Paystubs, tax information\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","roles":{}},{"id":"si17089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17268q3","for":"Slide17268q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17101","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17268q3","for":"Slide17268q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17113","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17268q3","for":"Slide17268q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17131","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17268q3","for":"Slide17268q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17143","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17268q3","for":"Slide17268q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17155","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17268q3","for":"Slide17268q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17200","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","roles":{}},{"id":"si17218","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17268q3","for":"Slide17268q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17230","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17268q3","for":"Slide17268q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17242","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17268q3","for":"Slide17268q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17254","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17268","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si16987","si16998","si17009","si17020","si17089","si17101","si17113","si17131","si17143","si17155","si17218","si17230","si17242","si17254"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17268"},"question":{"interactionId":"16943","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What does a patient put behind the Billing Information tab?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["3"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Slide17692","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17692"}}},{"id":"si17379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"1_5","roles":{}},{"id":"si17335","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17335_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_21","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Review it with the doctor\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si17346","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17350","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17346_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_22","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Throw it away\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_47","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17361","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_48","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17357_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_23","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Leave it at home\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17368","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_49","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17372","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_50","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17368_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_24","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Give it back to the doctor\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_51","roles":{}},{"id":"si17441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17620q4","for":"Slide17620q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17453","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17620q4","for":"Slide17620q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17465","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17620q4","for":"Slide17620q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17483","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17620q4","for":"Slide17620q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17495","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17620q4","for":"Slide17620q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17507","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17620q4","for":"Slide17620q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17552","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","roles":{}},{"id":"si17606","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17570","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17620q4","for":"Slide17620q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17582","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17620q4","for":"Slide17620q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17594","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17620q4","for":"Slide17620q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17620","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si17339","si17350","si17361","si17372","si17441","si17453","si17465","si17483","si17495","si17507","si17606","si17570","si17582","si17594"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17620"},"question":{"interactionId":"17295","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What does the patient do with the folder at follow-up appointments?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Slide17732","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":45},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17732"}}},{"id":"Slide12219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12219"}}},{"id":"Pool421","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":421,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"How To Use Discharge Folders","class":"project","title":"How To Use Discharge Folders","children":["Slide5444","Slide12274","Slide17633","Slide16200","Slide17672","Slide16556","Slide17712","Slide17268","Slide17692","Slide17620","Slide17732","Slide12219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":377,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12274q0","Slide16200q1","Slide16556q2","Slide17268q3","Slide17620q4"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":50,"passScore":40}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5444","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12274","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide17633","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide16200","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide17672","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide16556","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide17712","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide17268","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide17692","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide17620","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide17732","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide12219","title":"Slide 13"}]}